Hello everyone, this is Yuzuko Ito, I'm Suzuki Oozora no Yakushiki, I'm the one you've been waiting to see.
I'm Yuzuko Ito, I can't see the sand, this is Yuzuko Kanazawa, and this video is titled "I'm suddenly on the line with the members!
I'm going to show you how to make the most of the time you have left in your life.
I'm going to send a line to all the members and show you the various aspects of the race.
We'll have a scavenger hunt on the line, and a great comedy competition on the line.
We, the members, are here.
I can see how they communicate with each other and their private lives. I'm sure they're star members.
Let's start with the first race.
The first race is the first to get a reply from me.
I'm sure you'll all agree that the rule is that you don't tell the members.
I've already decided who I'm going to send it to, and I've already decided who I'm going to send it to.
I've already decided!
But the number you're talking about is Cocona, so I'm going with seven.
I'll do seven, a strengthened and more powerful, I'll do seven, a strengthened and more powerful, I'll do seven!
I'm sure it'll be read the moment I send it, but it's so fast, so fast, it's always on my record.
I'm sure you'll be able to read my messages the moment I send them to you.
I'll send it to you as soon as I can, I'll keep track.
I'm not sure if I'll ever be able to keep up with the slow ones... but I'm sure I'll be able to do one song.
But I'm a little confident I'll do one song, Suzu.
I know, I know... she's still a little bit... a little bit...
Power
Mar
Keep it with you
dea
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What? What's up? Did you get in?
First up is Coconut, who came in first.
That's what I was hoping for, sir.
I got your message right away. I'm watching Celebi.
I'm watching Celebi.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to take a bath now.
It's like a millimeter.
Millimeter millimeters.
I got 5 replies. What are you doing now? In.
I'm doing great.
It's so funny.
Next. 2nd place.
I sent it to Nana-chan and asked her what she was doing. She's taking her contacts off right now.
What's wrong? I got two of them.
I got two.
Thank you, Nana-chan.
You were fast.
Thank you.
Next.
Third place, Ami-chan.
Yes, I sent it to Ellen, so I got a voice message back.
Um, I sent it to Ellen, so I got a voice message back. Two seconds. Wanna hear it? Two seconds? What is it? Does it work?
I'm doing the dishes. Oh! I'm doing the dishes! You wrote back to me while I was doing the dishes. That's so sweet. You're so sweet.
I'm next. I was hoping for a little more. But you're pretty fast, even with this. Hagiwara Nokocchan. We're having yakiniku. What's up? What's up? We're the same. What's up? I said, "What's going on? Here it comes.
Everyone knows you're on YouTube, but you're still heavy on the singing. That's true. You told me to hang in there after this. You're early. Really, I love it here.
Even I send them and they get back to me that same number of minutes. Me too, once. The same number of minutes. It's really just a few seconds. Like three or four seconds. That's fast. I'll reply later.
Ki-Suzuki Hayase, 2 points? Or just 1 point? Congratulations!
Thanks COCONUT!
The second race is a scavenger hunt on line!
This is a race in which participants are asked to send a picture of something or other via LINE, and the first one to do so is the winner.
The person who comes first will be asked to send a picture of the food they have nearby.
If you are out of town or something...,
Yes, that kind of thing.
So we have to think about it.
That's right.
Who should I send it to from the group line of 23 people in blue?
So, you want to say it now, as a kabuta?
Let's say it now.
Se-no.
Yun-chan.
Yun, isn't that you? Kabuta and Yun-chan?
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, no!
Oh no, what should I do?
Yes, I'll do it.
I don't know, but let's make it a game.
Let's send a picture of the food we have nearby.
Send me a picture when I say "se-no". Se-no!
My stomach hurts! You have lycomin? That was quick, it's been gone for a while now.
I was just talking to her... she looks like she's sleeping.
No, he's not.
Who was that?
Aren't those four guys too early?
I wanted to show you.
Come on, let me see.
Show me what?
I'm sorry, I'm just a little preoccupied.
Rico, I think I've noticed something.
Rico!
I've got it! I've got it!
Natto!
Nab them!
It won't stick!
Don't look at me!
Okay, Ami, I'll send it to Yaegashi.
It came right away!
Here's a picture of Kalibo's gummies...
So cute!
So, what's up? He said...
I sent it to Riko Iwamoto, and within a minute or so...
They're so real!
She said she hadn't opened it yet.
Did you take it out of the fridge?
Didn't she?
I sent her a picture and...
What did I send you? It's ready.
Maybe he's working on your sister's case. Maybe she's working on her sister's case.
Izu-chan is Yuan-chan, but Anno didn't come at all.
He didn't show up. This is the one that probably won't show up.
It's frustrating. It's frustrating. I'll wait for a reply.
I'll wait for a reply, but maybe they'll send it after the shoot.
Congrats to Ami on the points.
And now, Ami, it's time for you to leave.
Okay.
Good work today.
Good work.
Let's go for it.
On the block.
Oh, block?
Bye-bye.
And now, let's switch gears for the third race.
This one is pretty difficult and probably a bit of a pain in the ass to watch.
I mean, some of the girls don't reply, do they?
What are you talking about? What are you talking about?
I think it's too hard.
The title of the big joke is
Thank you for watching.
What is the title of the movie that was a hit in the Jomon Era?
This is hard.
We've decided on a member for the big comedy.
I don't know.
Oh, something came.
It's from your brother.
You don't understand, do you?
No, I don't.
I'm not in on the project.
Wait a minute.
I thought Tsuriko-chan was good, didn't I?
I've already written a line.
That's right.
I have to remember the "yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I'm in the mood for a big comedy showdown at the "Jomon Era"....
I'm in the mood for a big joke match, and I'm in the mood for a good one, but I'm wondering if you'd seriously consider a survey, or a lens, or a lens, sure.
I'll think about it now or something... please don't ask me to do that...
Please, this is the snow, right?
Bread crusts, they were 50 yen at the bakery.
I have a lot of them!
I'm not saying don't tell me this, so I'm not going to tell you the answer to the snow question now... but in the semi, what was the title of the hit movie from the Jomon period?
Jomon Rhapsody.
No, no!
I like it, so don't go in there, Yukie
help me, this air, it looks like that Karen won't come, so I'll send it to Goat and A-chan, and I'll send it to Kudo Yua-chan
I'll send it to Yua Kudo.
I'll send it to Yuie Kudo...
Okay, here comes the transformation.
Penshin's here... and the transformation's here... and the transformation didn't come.
I'll think of a work and answer here...
Then, I moved in during the Seimon era.
I'm sorry Okuda dropped it. All of you remembered.
Yes, Yuzu-chan wrote it... what was the title of the movie that was a hit in the era of the two gates?
How to make Yayoi earthenware
Wait a minute...
Yuzu-chan!
How's it going?
Yuzu, you did it!
Yuzu, I'm done.
Yuzu, you made it.
You've got a glazed-over look in your eyes.
Yuzu-chan measures?
Yuzu-chan countermeasure
Countermeasure.
Yuzu-chan!
Oh no!
It's not good!
Yuzu!
Hey, I wonder if Yoochun's here.
I asked her to help me.
Hi, Yuzu!
She's not coming.
Hey!
It's Yuriya Miyakoshi.
Finally?
An answer?
What was the title of the hit movie in the Jomon Era?
We're the real kids.
Oh, my.
I'm so happy for you, Yuri.
Thank you, Yuri-chan!
Wait a minute, I got the second one from myself snow
Here comes the second installment!
What was the title of the movie that was a hit in the Jomon Era?
Jomon Chronicles of Hunting and Love
Snow!
Wait, wait, stop!
Yuu stamps are here too!
It's not done, yes
What was the title of the movie that was a hit in the Jomon Era?
Unforgettable, Love This You
Thank you for your hard work!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha...
What?
You look scared.
What do you mean?
I know what you mean.
Mr. Geramastaf is here.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm here. It's snowing right now.
Third...
Stop, stop, stop.
Hit the Jomon period.
What is the title of the movie?
Jomon Setsuko's Diary
Accompanied by a clay figurine
I like clay figures.
Like to accompany it.
I don't like snowflakes.
Does it have all the subtypes?
You want to.
That's great.
What's the point now?
Miyuna.
So, for now.
You know, out of all the people who sent me stuff...
You sent me the funniest one.
I'd like to give you an extra point.
You're right.
I'll never forget it.
What? Really?
What are you going to do, Yutachan?
Yeah, I'm excited.
Everyone, please.
I'm asking for everyone here.
We have one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Y. Imai Yuki's Jomon Rhapsody with a Dog doll.
Wow! Wait, wait!
Wait, this is so bad!
3 votes
Unforgettable love without face
Three votes!
Finally, a way to make it work....
Yay!
It's 3-3.
Let's give it to them here, too, shall we?
Sure, let's let these two decide.
Oh, well...
She should give it to me.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're already at 3-3.
The one who put it in for me.
Let's ask the one who gave it to me.
Oh, Y Imai Yuki's Jomon Rhapsody with Clay Figure
Ah, I don't know.
Then I'd like to read it out.
You, with your unforgettable love face
Why?
Wait, it's not right. It's too low.
For the third race, Yuna got one point for being early.
Yuna got a vote in the first race, so I get 1 point.
In total, Yuna gets 1 point and I get 2.
And Ami-chan has 1.
Yuzu has a chance to win.
I'd like to have one, so what about the fourth race?
I've decided on 100 million points.
The Final Showdown
The last and final showdown is for you to send us your favorite selfie of the last few days.
100 million points... and 100 million points... for the most difficult one.
Please, let's decide... who to send the best selfie to.
Who do you want to send it to?
I'm pretty sure Ai Kinoshita said she was in "sleep mode" or something.
That's suspicious.
I've decided.
You didn't structure it?
No.
I've decided, too, now.
Okay, okay.
Let's go for a walk.
Okay.
Ah, Hialien.
Oh, Yuho?
Ah!
First a goo, now a geppoi.
Oh, no!
Hitomi, let's go with Hitomi Hasegawa
Hitomi, you're fast!
No, Hitomi, you're fast.
You're early.
We've been talking.
Please.
Your next favorite
Selfie.
Send it to me.
I'll send it.
Here you go.
Okay.
Okay. - Okay.
Is this it?
I don't know.
This time of day is for everyone.
It's pretty much me time, right?
I mean...
Suzun doesn't really transform at this time of day.
I know.
I don't get it.
No, I can't! I can't!
Have you talked to anyone lately?
There's no one to talk to.
We've been talking.
Around here...
Wait, I'm in Akita.
Wait, I'm strong...
Here
I'm so cute, I've never taken a selfie before!
I'm here...
This is great!
I'm going to send it to Abby and Spearn.
I'll send it to Spian, and if he comes back, it'll be a miracle!
I'm sure he'll come when he gets back from Spian-chan, but he won't send me the pictures.
I'm so surprised by that stamp...
I'm sure he'll probably come, Mana, once he's recorded...
I'm sure you'll probably get it, Mana.
Hey!
Boo-boo! It's right this way.
It's so cute!
I guess that's how you make a tree... right? I didn't use my luck there.
I dared to use my luck here.
By the way, all the transformations came back.
And Yuki Imai sent in about three "Oikiri" (great comedy) pieces.
It was a tremendous effort!
Kokka Hagiwara said "What's wrong?" several times.
Riko, too... she's transformed herself, but I'm sorry, I haven't seen it yet...
As for me... first of all, Yoshimoto Cocona...
Aoi Anno is on YouTube right now.
I know...
I'll go with Nanako Shiogama.
Yua Kudo.
Yuriya Miyakoshi
Mana Mochinaga.
And Yua...
What was that, a big joke?
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
It was at the time of
I suspected that she was in the middle of filming.
So, um, she hasn't come since then.
So, I've probably been
I've been worrying about it for about 25 minutes.
I'm too worried about the great comedy
So, the final race is on!
Yuzu Ito, who was the first to reply.
100 million points. Thank you very much. 100 million points for being so nice.
So, the winner is Yayoi earthenware.
Congratulations!
Hey, it's gonna get picked up. Like this.
Cocoa, I'll make sure you use it. I'll make sure you use it.
How about a YouTube project? How to make Yayoi earthenware.
Oh, that's my style. Clay.
I'm going to have to make this.
Yes, you're responsible for it.
I'd like to know about the members' personal lives.
Like, their private life, or their line, or their usual life...
Oops...
You're in trouble. I think I've brought it to you.
It's from Heya-chan.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
It's from the Jomon Era...
Wait, 20...
I've been thinking about it for like 30 minutes.
I really can't.
It's too much fun.
He's a good kid.
Let's just finish this one up.
I'm sure we'll get it right. What was the title of the hit movie from the Jomon period?
The Great Maze of Vertical Habitats Bye-bye!
Come on, guys, it was all part of the plan.
Thanks for joining us. Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.